[{"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Who are you trying to reach", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Who are you trying to reach", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What number are you trying to reach", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I want to now who I'm talking to", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What do you think I said", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Jesus..", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " my friend? my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend? What the..", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What are you doing here", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Aha, my friend, you gave yourself away. Are you calling from work? my friend's on her way over", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I like that thing you're doing with your voice, my friend. It's sexy", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Maybe that's because I'm not my friend", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "The question is not who am I. The question is where am I", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "So who are you", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "So where are you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He's not registered. Could he have gone to another hotel", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We'll find him, my friend. Don't worry", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What are you doing with a cellular telephone, son", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You got some ideas of playing around, boy", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend was released. His cellular bill was clean. He didn't make those calls", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I know. We're checking every cellular account in the county. Any calls made to you or my friend are being cros", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You're absolutely right. I'm the first to admit it. If this were a scary movie, I'd be the prime suspect", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It's 199", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I called my dad", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "When you're arreste", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No, Sheriff my friend called your dad. I saw him", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I called my dad", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah...and when I called no one answered", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Stop. Right there", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Don't come any closer", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You have to play, my friend. Don't want to disappoint your dad. He's been waiting around all night", "docId": "Scream.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "And if you get it righ", "qsentId": 34}]